[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the character played by Robert De Niro in the 1980 movie Raging Bull?", "correct_answer": "Jake LaMotta", "incorrect_answers": ["Rocky Balboa", "Joey LaMotta", "Tommy Como"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mudpuppies hibernate in the winter months.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is depicted on Egypts national emblem, which is featured on the national flag of Egypt, adopted in 1984?", "correct_answer": "Eagle", "incorrect_answers": ["Bear", "Jackal", "Lion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is what mostly attracts a butterfly to a flower.", "correct_answer": "The flowers nectar", "incorrect_answers": ["The flowers color", "The flowers shape", "The flowers smell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was name of the evil cat in Disneys version of Cinderella?", "correct_answer": "Lucifer", "incorrect_answers": ["Sneaky Pete", "Satan", "Old Snakeeyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Mary Baileys maiden name in the 1946 classic Its a Wonderful Life?", "correct_answer": "Hatch", "incorrect_answers": ["Lamb", "Reed", "Wilson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The number of total calories, carbohydrates, fats, and sodium per serving is reported to be highest in which of the following meals?", "correct_answer": "Hardees Kids Meal - Slammers", "incorrect_answers": ["Burger King  WHOPPER JR.", "McDonalds Cheeseburger", "Wendys Jr. Hamburger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Finland?", "correct_answer": "Helsinki", "incorrect_answers": ["Prague", "Suva", "Malabo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the longest river in the United States of America?", "correct_answer": "Missouri", "incorrect_answers": ["Colorado", "Rio Grande", "Mississippi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the Razzie Award for Worst Actor for 1983?", "correct_answer": "Christopher Atkins for A Night in Heaven", "incorrect_answers": ["Barbra Streisand in drag for Yentl", "John Travolta for Two of a Kind", "John Travolta for Staying Alive"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie The Conversation, Harry Caul tears up his apartment.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The members of only one of these types of microorganisms have a cell nucleus. Which are they?", "correct_answer": "Algae", "incorrect_answers": ["Viruses", "Archaea", "Bacteria"]}]